welcome to ICICI Prudential video guy
you're watching a video on how to login
to your online account for your ICICI
Prudential life insurance policies visit
ICICI pro-life com click on login select
customer from the options you can log in
using your registered mobile number or
email ID enter your password and sign in
once logged in you can avail information
and transact in a simple and convenient
way if you're logging in for the first
time you can simply click on new user if
you do not remember your password or
want to change your password you can
simply click on change or forgot
password to set a new password enter the
required fields and click on submit you
can now log in with the new password so
go ahead and log into your ICICI proven
explore all the servicing options that
you can avail online thank you